blackview.hk 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy | BLACKVIEW

Blackview respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. And also describes other important topics relating to your privacy.

The policy of allowing access to this Personal Information is only to our staffs with a need to know. We also use available technology and encryption, when legally required or when appropriate for your protection, to provide a more secure environment and to reduce the chance of unauthorized access. Personal Information is stored in a secure environment protected by a combination of physical and technical measures. Tape backups are not permitted to leave the premises without prior authorization.

Your Consent

By using Blackview Internet Site or providing personal information to us, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy and any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements.

If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy (and any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements), do not use BLACKVIEW Internet Sites or Contact Us forms.

Information That Sent By Your Web Browser

Information Collected and Stored Automatically: If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the web site, read pages or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store information like the following concerning your visit.

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors—to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use.

Information That You Voluntarily Provide

We do not collect personally-identifiable information unless you choose to provide it to us. If you provide us with personally identifiable information, for example by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information only to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information and services that you request.

Submitting voluntary information constitutes your consent to the use of the information for the stated purpose. When a user clicks the “Submit” button on any of the Web forms found on our site they are indicating voluntary consent to use of the information they submit for the stated purpose. We do not collect or use information for commercial marketing.

Sharing of Information

BLACKVIEW will not sell personal information collected from its Internet sites to mailing list brokers without your express consent.

BLACKVIEW may share your personal information with other business units. When we do so, these other business units will use your information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you subsequently consented) and only as permitted under this Policy, any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements, and all applicable privacy and data protection laws.

BLACKVIEW may also share your personal information with third parties we hire to perform support services for us. These third parties are required to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf and to treat your personal information as strictly confidential.

In some cases, BLACKVIEW may share your personal information with third parties who partner with us to provide products and services to our customers. When we do so, we will require our business partners to use the personal information we share with them in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you subsequently consented) and only as permitted under this Policy, any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements, and all applicable privacy and data protection laws.

In certain, limited circumstances we may share or transfer personal information to unrelated third parties. For example, we may provide personal information to a third party (i) at your request; (ii) to comply with a legal requirement or court order; (iii) to investigate a possible crime, such as identity theft; (iv) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of 3M or a 3M business unit; or (v) under similar circumstances. If such an event occurs, we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information.

Information Protection

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, our site system would employ software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. If such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials.

How Information Is Used

The information we collect is used for a variety of purposes (e.g., to respond to requests for information about our products and services and to fill orders). We make every effort to disclose clearly how information is used at the point where it is collected so that our users can determine for themselves whether they wish to provide the information.

Retention of Information

BLACKVIEW retains the personal information collected on BLACKVIEW internet sites as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law.

Interaction with Children

BLACKVIEW internet sites are generally not intended for persons under 13 years of age. BLACKVIEW does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children on its Internet Sites except as permitted under applicable law. If your child has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be deleted from our records, you may do so by using the feedback mechanisms provided at a particular BLACKVIEW internet site, by clicking on this feedback link

Changes to this Policy and our Privacy Statements

BLACKVIEW reserves the right to update or modify this Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our BLACKVIEW internet sites. We also reserve the right to update or modify our Country or Web Site Privacy Statements, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised Privacy Statement on the applicable BLACKVIEW internet site. If we modify this Policy or any Privacy Statement, the modifications will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy or Privacy Statement on the applicable BLACKVIEW internet site.
